

Ahmed Zeinhom Attia

ACCOUNTANT

CONTACT

Al gharbia ,Almahalla alkoubra ,Qasm 2 ,sekt zeft

01276688569

01023973326

Ahmedzenhom225@gmail.com

in Ahmed-Zeinhom-318696162

SKILLS

Computer skills :very good

Arabic: native

English: very good

REFERENCES

Available on request.

Available to work outside the country.

PROFILE

A highly organized, detail orientated and dependable professional who has the ability to apply her accounting knowledge and experience to a diverse range of financial issues. I'm a hard-working, dedicated and ambitious Accountant who possesses strong theoretical and practical knowledge of generally accepted accounting principles.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Oct.2020 – Present Set Elhabiab store for household goods Owner and manager – Almahalla Alkoubra

- I supervise the day to day operations of store, selling goods,
- executing money management,
- improve services and getting feedback from customers.

Jan.2020 – Dec.2020 Suez canal for life insurance insurance sales representative – Almahalla Alkoubra .

- Designing and implementing effective marketing strategies to sell new insurance contracts,
- Contacting potential clients and creating rapport by networking.

10 June 2019 –10 July 2019 Banking trainee – Almahalla Alkoubra **ALEXBANK**

 Working to understand banking operations and procedures by performing assigned projects and responsibilities throughout various banking departments including financial analysis, customer service, human resource management.

20 June 2018-20 July 2018

QNB ALAhli Bank

Banking trainee – Almahalla Alkoubra

- Addition to pervious duties ,learning how to open account for client and procedures for opening.
- How to deal with clients .

COURSES

February 2018-April 2018 Professional financial accountant

Ain Shams University

February 2018-April 2018 Diploma in Professional comprehensive accountant

International Academy for Training

Relevant modules:

- The preparation of financial statements,
- The course of financial accounting, commercial companies,
- The course of taxation, contracting companies, import &export.

February 2018-April 2018 Diploma in electronic accounting programs

International Academy for Training

Relevant modules:

• Peachtree, Quick Books and Accounting Excel.

EDUCATION

2016 – 2020 bachelor of commerce department of Accounting (English section)

Grade: very good Tanta university

2013 – 2016 3GCSE Talaat Harb secondary school